https://www.ctjfs.org/privacy-policy/

Group Counseling and Support Group
Parenting Education Program (PEP) and Focus on Kids (FOK)
Home Companion Program
Jewish Twenties and Thirties (JTT)
Joan and Ben Zinbarg Camp Scholarship Program
Kuriansky Family Counseling
Individual and Family Counseling
Group Counseling and Support Groups
Parenting Education Program (PEP) and Focus on Kids (FOK)
Group Counseling and Support Group
Parenting Education Program (PEP) and Focus on Kids (FOK)
Home Companion Program
Jewish Twenties and Thirties (JTT)
Joan and Ben Zinbarg Camp Scholarship Program
Kuriansky Family Counseling
Individual and Family Counseling
Group Counseling and Support Groups
Parenting Education Program (PEP) and Focus on Kids (FOK)
Privacy PolicyDonor Privacy Policy
Schoke Jewish Family Service is committed to respecting the privacy of our donors.
We have developed this privacy policy to ensure our donors that donor information will not be shared with any third party.
This policy is in effect for both online and offline donations.
Awareness
Schoke Jewish Family Service provides this Donor Privacy Policy to make you aware of our privacy policy, and to inform you of the way your information is used.
We also provide you with the opportunity to remove your name from our mailing list, if you desire to do so.
Information Collected:
•	Contact information:
name, address, phone number, email;
•	Payment information: billing information;
•	Information you wish to share: questions, comments, suggestions; and
•	Your request to receive periodic updates
How Information is UsedSchoke Jewish Family Service uses your information to understand your needs and provide you with better service.
Specifically, we use your information to help you complete a transaction, communicate back to you, and update you on agency happenings.
Credit card numbers are used only for donation or payment processing and are not retained for other purposes.
We use the comments you offer to provide you with information requested, and we take seriously each recommendation as to how we might improve communication.
No Sharing of Personal InformationSchoke
Jewish Family Service will not sell, rent, or lease your personal information to other organizations.
We assure you that the identity of all our donors will be kept confidential.
Use of donor information will be limited to the internal purposes of Jewish Family Service of Stamford.
Removing Your Name From Our Mailing List
It is our desire to not send unwanted mail to our donors.
Please contact us if you wish to be removed from our mailing list.
Contact UsContacting Us.
If you have comments or questions about our donor privacy policy, please contact Matt Greenberg at 203-921-4161 or mgreenberg@ctfs.org
Type and Press “enter” to Search
For Information About Upcoming Programs – Sign Up Here
To Become a Volunteer – Sign Up Here
x
We Need Your Help!
Schoke JFS helps over 5,000 families a year.
Help us to reach our year-end fundraising goal by clicking here.
If you need assistance, go to our homepage by clicking here.
CLOSE
